I know it may not seem like it, but there are very few actors who are actually wealthy.
Then there are some actors who are rich.
But for the most part, the actors that make up the entertainment industry are working check to check.
I was super duper fortunate to, at the age of 35, land on a television show that ended up being iconic.
And it afforded me the opportunity to get financial stability for the first time in my life.
I have been an actress since I was eight years old.
I've been a Screen Actors Guild since 1994.
Acting did not afford me financial stability till I was 35.
This is because the industry itself is not made for actors.
It's not made for crew.
It's not made for creatives.
The industry is made for the industry.
The creatives and the actors are deciding, well, we have to protect ourselves.
But that's not for everybody.
And it shouldn't have to be because ultimately the business that is betting on the business that is created from what we're doing should actually support us.
So I say all that to say that as you're watching people on their feeds talking about the writer's strike with the WGA, the Writers Guild of America, and the now actor's strike with SAG, the Screen Actors Guild of America slash AFTRA.
What you're seeing is the people who are making the shows you love, the movies you love, the projects that you love saying, hey, we know that you execs got money because people love this work.
And they love this work, not because of you, but because of us.
And so we should get to reap the benefits that you guys are reaping.
Labor unions are created because laborers are exploited.
And that happens in every field when it comes to capitalism.
Ba-dum-bum!
Union Strong.
Lion Strong.
llev
Vas
Y